(Amy:)Human beings form
emotional attachments as they grow up.
ln your case, to your mother,
superheroes, et cetera.
(Amy:)I'm going to attempt an experiment...
(Amy:)...that will get you
to transfer those feelings to me.
(Sheldon:)Well, seems what's on
the menu tonight...
(Sheldon:)...is malarkey
with a big side of poppycock.
(Amy:)We'll see. Let's start with
a little romantic dinner music, shall we?
l see what you're doing.
You're attempting to build on the work...
(Sheldon:)...of Ebbinghaus by triggering
an involuntary memory...
(Sheldon:)...of me playing that game.
(Sheldon:)Admittedly the happiest 600 hours
of my childhood.
(Sheldon:)- But it won't work.
- Fine.
There's no reason we can't have a lovely
dinner. Why don't you have a seat?
- May I offer you something to drink?
- You know I don't drink.
(Amy:)Not even Strawberry Quik?